-Yes? -Guess who?
-喂？ -猜我是谁？
TEE-HEE!
（讨厌）
Hello, Eita.
我知道，是瑛太
Is this a bad time?
你现在忙吗？
I was calibrating my mouse.
我在调节鼠标
You sure are carefree.
还真闲耶
*CALIBRATING MEANS ADJUSTING MOUSE SENSITIVITY
（调节鼠标灵敏度）
Anyway, you're coming over today, right?
对了，你今天会来我家吧？
For Runa's lesson?
来当瑠奈的家教
So then the schedule hasn't changed?
果然预定没有变啊
Not that I know of.
不是这样吗？
When you come over,
你来的时候
can you bring that manga we talked about?
把上次提到的漫画带来
I really wanna read it.
我想看
Sure.
可以啊
Yay! You're the best, Yamada.
最爱山田了
Okay, see you then.
好，那晚点见
Sure! Next Saturday, huh?
嗯，下星期六嘛
Sounds good.
嗯，没问题
Runa wants to hang out with me!
我跟瑠奈约了要出去玩
I'm glad.
好开心
SATURDAY, OCTOBER 3RD
（星期六）
ORIGINAL STORY BY MASHIRO
（原作：Mashiro）
My, my…
说真的…
I never imagined Princess Ruri's player
没想到瑠璃姬大人本人
would be a real, charming young lady.
真的是名女性，而且如此可爱
Based on past experience,
根据我的经验
I was 100% certain that the player was a man.
本人有100%的概率会是男性
Of course, I was still prepared to love them,
即便如此，我也做好全心去爱的准备
but behold, a genuine specimen of blooming female beauty.
结果竟是如此年轻貌美的女性
It seems I still have much to learn.
看来我观察得还不够透澈
Um…
那个…
I hate to go over this again.
我刚才说很多遍了
-I'm not Princess Ruri-- -Furthermore.
-我并不是瑠璃姬… -话虽如此
I never dreamed that I would actually be able to meet you.
我做梦也没想到有机会见到本人
When I heard
听说在FOS
that you were playing FOS as Princess Ruri,
你也是用“瑠璃姬”这个名字
I followed and switched from the previous game,
我就从上个游戏追来了
but to think you were aware of me.
没想到你知道我的存在
Maintaining her adorable charm
不只是可爱
and immediately reaching high rank,
在任何游戏都能立刻登上排名
no matter what the game,
成为知名玩家
is the Princess Ruri way.
这只有瑠璃姬大人才办得到
As a fan, you've always made me proud.
身为粉丝，我深感荣耀
SORRY, I'LL BE LATE
（我临时有事会晚到 我认识的网友应该到了）
BUT A FRIEND WILL BE THERE
（你们先聊，抱歉哦）
Your latest achievements have been no different.
这次竟能以这样的方式见面
If it would not be an affront…
如果可以的话
-Umm… -I would like to join your guild.
-那个… -我希望能加入瑠璃姬大人的公会
Sorry, I need to use the restroom!
抱歉，我去个洗手间
Very well.
了解
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Runa hasn't come
瑠奈没有来
and a stranger was at our meeting point.
却有陌生人出现在碰面地点
Princess Ruri!
瑠璃姬大人
You're Princess Ruri, are you not?
你是瑠璃姬大人，对吧？
-Princess Ruri! -He's convinced I'm Princess Ruri.
-瑠璃姬大人… -他误会我是瑠璃姬
-And he won't listen to a word I say!
-而且完全不听我说话
Coming!
来了
Welcome, Yamada-kun.
山田，欢迎你
Hello.
你好
You're as handsome as ever.
你还是一样帅耶
Runa's locked away in her room playing games all day.
瑠奈老是关在房间里打电玩
I worry whether she'll actually pass the exam for your high school.
不晓得她那样考不考得上你的学校
Runa!
瑠奈
"Professor" Yamada is here.
山田老师来咯
Yamada!
山田
Hi.
你好
I'll let you two get to it!
那就交给你了
Right.
好的
Don't slack off now, Runa.
要好好用功哦
I'm not!
我本来就有啊
I did all the pages you told me to.
瑠奈有乖乖写到你规定的地方哦
Look!
你看9
Runa, today…
瑠奈，你…
Don't you have somewhere else to be?
今天应该有什么约吧？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Well,
没事
if I'm wrong, then that's fine.
是我误会就算了
CALL FROM AKANE
（茜来电）
How could I have anywhere else to be?
我什么约都没有啊
CALLING RUNA SASAKI
（佐佐木瑠奈，拨号中）
No answer…
瑠奈果然没接啊
I'm in a fix.
真是伤脑筋
Lunch alone with a total stranger…
和陌生人单独相处啊
Excuse me, Princess Ruri.
那个…瑠璃姬大人
I apologize for the intrusion,
冒昧请问一下
but is that you in there, Princess Ruri?
瑠璃姬大人在这里吗？
This is the women's restroom.
这里是女厕耶
Is this for real?
不会吧？
Princess Ruri, are you all right?
瑠璃姬大人，你没事吧？
I, uh… have a stomachache.
我的肚子…有点痛…
Also, this is the women's rest--
话说，这里是女厕吧…
I knew it.
果然没错
-It's as I expected. -Um…
-我就猜到是这样 -那个…
-When you didn't return, I worried. -This is…
-看你没回来，我就很担心 -这里是…
-I thought you might have collapsed. -Damn it…
-怕你在厕所失去意识 -那个…
Excuse me,
听我说！
but I do believe this is the women's restroom!
这里应该是女厕吧！
Princess Ruri,
瑠璃姬大人
would you mind opening the door?
你可以开门吗？
If you could, please.
可不可以开门呢？
Princess Ruri…
瑠璃姬大人
It's not that big a deal.
反正…又不是什么大事
She's probably gone home already.
或许她已经回去了
In other words, you stood her up.
换句话说，你放了她鸽子？
It's nothing like that.
才没有放鸽子
I had someone from the online game go instead of me.
瑠奈有请游戏的网友代替赴约了
From the online game?
游戏的网友？
This guy who's a big fan of Eita's character.
好像是哥哥那个角色的狂粉
I invited him through Eita's account,
我用哥哥的账号约了他后
and he was really excited.
他高兴得不得了
Where are you going, Yamada?
山田，你要去哪？
Where did you agree to meet?
你们约在哪里碰面？
Why do you ask?
为何问这个？
Why…?
你还问？
This is way too dangerous. I'd better check on her.
这样太危险了 我去看看情况
What about my lesson?
瑠奈的家教呢？
I'll be right back. Continue with your textbook.
我马上就回来，你先自己写题目
Wait!
等等
You startled me.
吓死我了
I thought it was suddenly an auto door.
我还以为是自动门
I BROUGHT SNACKS
（我拿慰劳品来了）
Eita…
瑛太
Something wrong?
怎么了？
Whoa, she really did contact someone through my account.
还真的用我的账号传了信息
Talk about a mean trick.
有够恶劣
Where did they agree to meet?
碰面地点在哪里？
Let's see…
我看看…
Oh, it's close by.
还蛮近的
About 15 minutes by car.
从这里开车大概15分钟吧
Why…?
为什么…
Runa!
瑠奈
Runa! What shall we play today?
瑠奈，今天要玩什么？
Why can't things just stay as they are?
为什么不能这样持续下去呢？
Is it true?!
听说小茜…
Akane was kidnapped
被这一类的黑道人士带走了
by a criminal organization?!
是真的吗？
A-Aka-Aka…
小…小茜…
I may have exaggerated a little.
我好像说得太夸张了
Akane!
小茜！
Thanks for driving us, Mr. Kamota.
鸭田先生，谢谢你开车来
Mr. Kamota, you needed to turn right at that intersection.
鸭田先生，刚才的十字路口要右转
Mr. Kamota, we're going the wrong way.
鸭田先生，你越开越远了
When we find Akane, you have to apologize.
等见到Akane，要好好道歉哦
No way!
我才不道歉
Stop behaving like this.
给我差不多一点
This is exactly why you can't make friends at school.
你就是这样，才会在学校也被讨厌
Who needs them?
我又没差
I have 300 friends on the Internet.
反正我在网络上有300个好友
Akane! What do we do, Yamada-kun?!
小茜！ 怎么办啊，山田？
Mr. Kamota, keep your eyes on the road.
鸭田先生，请看前面
All anyone cares about is Akane. It's so stupid.
大家都在小茜长小茜短的，有够蠢
In the first place, why did you let her in our guild
说到底，为什么没经过瑠奈同意
without asking me?
就让那种人加入公会？
Look…
我说啊…
IT'S MY GUILD, YOU KNOW.
（那是我创的公会耶…）
When long-time users keep newbies out,
如果老手总是在排挤新人
content only gets worse.
游戏只有衰退一途
Be more welcoming.
你要懂得宽容
What do you mean?
那算什么？
Akane…
对方
was trying to be friends with you, wasn't she?
是真心想和你做朋友吧？
Next Saturday, huh?
下星期六嘛
Sounds good.
嗯，没问题
24-HOUR PARKING EMPTY
（24小时停车场）
Okay, shall we split up and look?
好，大家分头找吧
Akane!
小茜…
Mr. Kamota, you're heavy.
鸭田先生，这样很重
Wh-wh-wh-where…
在哪…
-Found her. -That was quick!
-找到了 -好快！
How did you know?
亏你认得出来
Still, something…
但是看起来…
seems off.
不太对劲…
Aka--
茜…
Akane!
小茜！
Aka-Aka-Aka…
小…
I'm so glad you're all right!
幸好你没事
Mr. Kamota?
鸭田先生？
Everything's fine.
你不用担心
Just leave the rest to the adults.
剩下就交给大人处理吧
And who might you be?
请问您是哪一位呢？
I'm the President of Kamota Strawberry Farm,
我是鸭田草莓农园代表人
Takezo Kamota!
我叫鸭田竹藏
I have friends who are lawyers!
我有朋友在当律师
Violence and blackmail are useless against me!
我绝不会屈服于暴力
We'll fight our battles in court!
让我们在法庭上对决吧
Akane, are you okay?
Akane，你没事吧？
Eita!
瑛太
Yamada too?
连山田也在
What are you guys doing here?
你们为什么会来这里？
Runa said she invited a stranger,
听说瑠奈找了不认识的人来
so we came to check if you were okay.
我们觉得担心，就来看看
What happened to your leg?
你的脚怎么了？
Oh, that's…
这个嘛…
My apologies. It was my fault.
抱歉，这是我害的
I surprised her in the women's restroom and--
因为我在女厕吓到她…
Tell me everything.
请你解释清楚吧
You're too close.
你太近了
I surmised that Princess Ruri may have fainted in the restroom
我怕瑠璃姬大人在厕所昏倒
and attempted to deliver her medicine.
便想把药拿给她
Princess Ruri,
瑠璃姬大人
are you unable to open the door?
你开不了门吗？
In that case…
那么…
I'll pass them under.
我从下面递给你
PAINKILLERS
（止痛药）
Princess Ruri?
瑠璃姬大人？
INCREDIBLE PAIN PAINKILLERS
（剧痛，止痛药）
That sums it up.
就是这么回事
She overreacted in surprise,
因为过于惊吓
and hit a weak spot against the toilet.
让她的小腿前侧不小心撞到马桶
Anyone would be surprised by that!
那样任何人都会吓到吧！
That's strange.
真奇怪
My mother taught me that when a female
如果发现女生在厕所不舒服
locks herself in the bathroom, you should stay quiet and slip her painkillers.
妈妈告诉我要默默递上止痛药
Don't apply your twisted upbringing to the rest of the world!
不要根据那种有限知识来行动
Also, stay out of the women's restroom!
首先你根本不该闯入女厕！
You are a rather uncouth fellow.
真是个没礼貌的人
What's your relationship with Princess Ruri?
你跟瑠璃姬大人是什么关系？
You're the one person I won't tell.
我不想跟你说
Are we done yet?
随便你们了
Yo!
嗨
You came to check on me?
听说你因为担心，就跑来了？
Thanks a lot.
谢谢了
No, forgive me.
不会，抱歉
Why are you apologizing?
为什么你要道歉啊？
Well…
要是我…
If I had told you I was tutoring Runa today…
有说今天要当瑠奈的家教就好了
You're her tutor?
山田是瑠奈的家教啊
Yes.
是的
I see.
这样啊
That's why Runa couldn't come.
难怪瑠奈今天来不了
-Um, I'm not sure-- -So that's all it was!
-这个嘛，该怎么说… -什么嘛，原来如此
Runa?
瑠奈？
The pain…
好…
It hurts!
痛！
You're… injured?
你…受伤了？
-I'm sorry. -Runa!
-抱歉… -瑠奈
Come with me.
过来
You're in for a scolding.
我要骂你一顿
Don't look to me for help.
我不会救你的
What you did was really dangerous.
这次你真的做了危险的事
Please learn your lesson.
请你好好反省
Let's go.
走了
Ow…
好…
Ow-ow-ow!
好痛…痛死了
Akane?
Akane？
My stomach hurts, suddenly.
肚子突然好痛
Your stomach? Not your leg?
肚子痛？不是脚痛吗？
Oh, uh…
不是啦，好像…
The pain may be spreading, or…
连肚子也传染到痛了
Perhaps you should administer the pills I gave you earlier?
服用我刚才给的止痛药如何？
You're not to speak to Akane!
不准你跟小茜讲话！
He's still here?
他还在啊
HMM…
（嗯…）
Not those.
那种不行
Those won't help.
根本没有效
Only Class-1 anti-inflammation pills
必须是由药剂师开药
from the drug store will do.
第一类医药品的止痛药才行
Class… huh?
第一类…什么？
If you walk 500 meters toward the station,
往车站方向走500米
there'll be a drugstore on your right.
右边就有间药局
Right. We'll go right away.
好，我马上去买
I'll go.
瑠奈去买…
Rub my belly.
帮我揉肚子…
Oh, and I worry that Eita can't find them alone.
只交给瑛太去买，我会不放心
Yamada and Mr. Kamota, please go with him.
山田和鸭田先生也跟着去吧
As for you, please go home!
还有你已经可以回去了
So Runa, what's your level?
瑠奈的等级有多高？
Sorry, I mean in-game.
抱歉，我在说游戏的事
Um…
这个嘛…
I've maxed out twice and since then…
两只满等，其他随便练练
Oh, then I guess we can't hunt together.
那就不能一起去打怪了
I'm still low-level.
因为我的等级很低
It won't work if there's a gap in levels, right?
等级差太多不适合组队吧？
I invited Yamada once, but he turned me down.
我之前约山田时，就被拒绝了
You want to hunt together?
一起打怪吗？
Our levels are too far apart.
我们等级差太多，不太好吧？
The experience penalties are a pain.
经验值惩罚很烦
It doesn't bother me.
瑠奈一点也不介意
Actually, I have low-level characters too.
更何况我也有等级低的角色
Then let's hunt together some time!
那下次一起去打怪吧
My class is Paladin.
我玩的职业是圣骑士
-But what's-- -How can you talk to me like that?
-瑠奈你… -为何你能和我正常说话？
Didn't you think it was strange
你不觉得怪吗？
that I never came?
都被我放鸽子了
Oh, uh, well…
那个…
I stood you up on purpose!
我是故意放你鸽子的
I wanted to cause you trouble.
希望你感到困扰
I don't like you, after all!
因为我讨厌茜
I wanted you to leave the guild!
想把你赶出公会
I thought that if I set you up
让你碰到怪人的话
with a weird guy, you'd start hating online games.
我猜你就会讨厌在线游戏…
I did think it was strange, but…
我就觉得有鬼
NOW I GET IT…
（原来如此…）
You're… injured?
你…受伤了？
I think I'll leave the lecture
说教…
to your brother.
就交给你哥吧
After all, I came today to make friends with you.
我今天是来和瑠奈当朋友的
Everyone's so nice.
大家都是好人
I've been thinking lately of how glad I am to have joined this guild.
我最近好庆幸自己能加入这个公会
But the other members are important companions to you, right?
但他们都是你的重要伙伴吧？
That's why…
所以我今天
I wanted to ask you to let me be your companion too.
是希望瑠奈也能让我成为一分子
What do you say, Runa?
才会来这里
I'm so sorry.
对不起…
I'm sorry I was mean to you!
对你使坏，真的很抱歉
Puberty is tough on girls, huh?
思春期的女生真难懂啊
I didn't expect her to butt heads with Akane like this.
没想到她会这样捉弄小茜
I'm at my wit's end!
我已经束手无策了
She was so cute and well-behaved when she was younger.
小时候的她明明那么率真可爱
What should I do?
我该怎么办才好？
Welcome back!
你们回来啦
MEDICINE
（药）
Akane, is your stomach feeling better?
小茜，你的肚子没事了吗？
Huh? Oh, yeah…
什么？是啊
I'm fine now.
完全没事了
Maybe Runa rubbing my belly helped.
大概是有瑠奈帮我揉肚子吧
It's unfortunate.
真是多灾多难
You were looking forward to today, weren't you?
你今天明明那么期待
And yet Runa tricked you.
却被瑠奈设计了
Well, once I saw
我也该反省啦
that there was a stranger here,
一看到陌生人在场
I should have gone straight home.
就应该直接回去才对
I'm a little irritated, of course.
虽然我的确有点不高兴
But I'm more disappointed that we didn't get to hang out.
但是无法和瑠奈玩更让我遗憾
Still, just watch.
不过你放心吧
I'm not the best at romance,
我虽然不太会谈恋爱
but I'm pretty good
换成和女生相处
at getting along with other girls.
我倒是挺擅长的
So I'm sure we'll be friends.
所以我们一定会变好朋友的
Eventually…
总有一天啦
You live up to expectations, Princess Ruri.
瑠璃姬大人果然厉害
I'd heard rumors of your generosity,
的确如传闻一样体贴
but you truly are a muse.
简直就是女神
Please honor me by dating with the expectation of marr--
请和我以结婚为前提交往…
Go home, already!
你请回吧！